streetsideauto.com 2017-03-14

# Privacy | StreetsideAuto.com

For each visitor within StreetSide Auto's Web sites, our Web server automatically recognizes the visitor's domain name. We also collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail; aggregate information on what pages visitors access; and information volunteered by the visitor, such as survey information and/or site registrations. 

Visitors may be asked to provide personal information, including name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address, on the StreetSide Auto website. In addition if a purchase is made, we collect credit card information, billing and shipping address, customer information, vehicle information, and other useful information pertaining to the purchase. This information may be gathered when the visitor registers for services, makes purchases via the website or sends the information to StreetSide Auto via an e-mail communication. If you choose to provide your personal information to StreetSide Auto, you agree that we may contact you to provide you with information that may be of interest to you. 

* * *

Use of the Information We Collect

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web site, to notify visitors who request it about updates to our site, and may be used to contact visitors for marketing purposes, and to alert you on updated information and services. We also use the information you voluntarily provide to fulfill your request, help you quickly find and/or receive information about StreetSide Auto or one of its affiliated companies, provide more complete service and answer your questions. Except as otherwise stated, we do not share customer-specific information with other organizations. The information may be used to confirm and process orders, to keep the customer informed about the status of his or her order, to obtain reviews, ratings or testimonials related to the customer's experience with StreetSide Auto website and products purchased. Further, customer-specific information may also be provided to third parties for tracking purposes, to charge the customer's credit card or process the customer's check or money order, as appropriate, and to fill and deliver the order. 

Visitors who supply us with their telephone numbers online may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders or requests they have placed online. 

Security

Given the nature of the Internet and the fact that no security system is perfect, StreetSide Auto cannot promise that the information you provide will never be obtained by unauthorized persons. StreetSide Auto does, however, utilize industry-standard practices to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, misuse, alteration and destruction. Such measures include using firewalls and security layers to protect certain sensitive transmissions of information. In some areas of our Web site, we may require a user ID and password for you to access information. StreetSide Auto will not disclose such passwords to third parties; however, you are responsible for maintaining the privacy and security of your password. 

StreetSide Auto may disclose your personal information in order to respond to a subpoena, court order, law enforcement agency or other such governmental agency's request, or as otherwise required by law. Your personal information may be disclosed if StreetSide Auto files for bankruptcy or if there is a transfer of assets or ownership, such as a merger or acquisition. 

* * *

Links to Non-StreetSide Auto Site

For the convenience of our users, this site may contain links to Web sites owned by third parties. Often, but not always, you can tell that you have linked to a non-StreetSide Auto Web site because the Web site will open a separate browser window. Links by StreetSide Auto to such external Web sites do not imply endorsement by StreetSide Auto of that company, its site or its privacy policy. StreetSide Auto is not responsible for the content of any linked sites and makes no representations regarding the content or accuracy of materials on such sites. If you decide to visit any third-party sites using links from this Web site, you do so at your own risk. 

Changes to Our Privacy Policy

StreetSide Auto reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time. If we decide to change our policy regarding privacy, we will post the revised privacy policy on our site. You may want to visit this site periodically to review the current privacy policy. Use of our site after the posting of a revised privacy policy constitutes your agreement with the revised policy. This privacy policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or legal rights in or on behalf of any party. 

For any questions regarding any of the policies we have on StreetsideAuto.com, we can be reached via our Contact Page. 

Children's Privacy Policy

This site may contain energy-related facts and information that could be of educational interest to children. StreetSide Auto does not gather personal information online from or about children. We encourage all children to seek consent of their parents or guardian before providing any information, in any form, about themselves or their household to anyone on the Internet. 

A Note for Parents on Children's Privacy Policy

StreetSide Auto closely scrutinizes its marketing and public information efforts, including this site, to conform to the guidelines put forth by the Children's Advertising Review Unit and the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. We encourage you to monitor your children's online time. We further ask that you help us protect their privacy by instructing them never to provide personal information on any Web site without your permission.
